♪ Ladies up in here tonight ♪
♪ No fighting ♪
♪ We got the refugees up in here ♪
♪ Shakira, Shakira ♪
♪ I never really knew that
she could dance like this ♪
♪ She make a man wants to speak Spanish ♪
♪ Cómo se llama, sí ♪
♪ Bonita, sí ♪
♪ Mi casa ♪
♪ Shakira, Shakira ♪
♪ Oh, baby, when you talk like that ♪
♪ You make a woman go mad ♪
♪ So be wise, sí ♪
♪ And keep on, sí ♪
♪ Reading the signs of my body ♪
♪ I'm on tonight ♪
♪ You know my hips don't lie ♪
♪ And I'm starting to feel it's right ♪
♪ All the attraction, the tension ♪
♪ Don't you see, baby,
this is perfection ♪
♪ Hey, girl, I can see your body moving ♪
♪ And it's driving me crazy ♪
♪ And I didn't have the slightest idea ♪
♪ Until I saw you dancing ♪
♪ And when you walk up
on the dance floor ♪
♪ Nobody cannot ignore the
way you move your body, girl ♪
♪ And everything so unexpected ♪
♪ The way you right and left it ♪
♪ So you can keep on shaking it ♪
♪ I never really knew that
she could dance like this ♪
♪ She make a man wants to speak Spanish ♪
♪ Cómo se llama, sí ♪
♪ Bonita, sí ♪
♪ Mi casa ♪
♪ Shakira, Shakira ♪
♪ Oh, baby, when you talk like that ♪
♪ You make a woman go mad ♪
♪ So be wise and keep on ♪
♪ Reading the signs of my body ♪
♪ I'm on tonight ♪
♪ You know my hips don't lie ♪
♪ And I am starting to feel you, boy ♪
♪ Come on, let's go, real slow ♪
♪ Don't you see, baby, así es perfecto ♪
♪ They know I am on
tonight, my hips don't lie ♪
♪ And I'm starting to feel it's right ♪
♪ All the attraction, the tension ♪
♪ Don't you see, baby,
this is perfection ♪
♪ Oh, boy, I can see your body moving ♪
♪ Half animal, half man ♪
♪ I don't, don't really
know what I'm doing ♪
♪ But you seem to have a plan ♪
♪ My will and self-restraint ♪
♪ Have come to fail now, fail now ♪
♪ See, I am doing what I can,
but I can't so you know ♪
♪ That's a bit too hard to explain ♪
♪ Baila en la calle de noche ♪
♪ Baila en la calle de día ♪
♪ I never really knew that
she could dance like this ♪
♪ She make a man wants to speak Spanish ♪
♪ Cómo se llama, sí ♪
♪ Bonita, sí ♪
♪ Mi casa ♪
♪ Shakira, Shakira ♪
♪ Oh, baby, when you talk like that ♪
♪ You know you got me hypnotized ♪
♪ So be wise and keep on ♪
♪ Reading the signs of my body ♪
♪ Señorita, feel the conga ♪
♪ Let me see you move like
you come from Colombia ♪
♪ Ladies, sí ♪
♪ Mira en Barranquilla
se baila así, say it ♪
♪ En Barranquilla se baila así ♪
♪ Yeah, she's so sexy,
every man's fantasy ♪
♪ A refugee like me back with the Fugees ♪
♪ From a third world country ♪
♪ I go back like when 'Pac
carried crates for Humpty Humpty ♪
♪ We leave the whole club dizzy ♪
♪ Why the CIA wanna watch us ♪
♪ Colombians and Haitians ♪
♪ I ain't guilty, it's
a musical transaction ♪
♪ Bo bop so bop, no more
do we snatch ropes ♪
♪ Refugees run the seas
'cause we own our own boats ♪
♪ I'm on tonight, my hips don't lie ♪
♪ And I'm starting to feel you, boy ♪
♪ Come on, let's go, real slow ♪
♪ Baby, like this is perfecto ♪
♪ Oh, you know I'm on
tonight, my hips don't lie ♪
♪ And I am starting to feel it's right ♪
♪ The attraction, the tension ♪
♪ Baby, like this is perfection ♪
♪ No fighting ♪